Let's revisit the Android flavor app from the last lesson.
我们再来看看上节课中提到的 Android Flavor 应用
So if we can understand how the Android flavor app displays an image
如果我们知道 Android Flavor 应用是如何
per list item, then we can do something similar in our Miwok app.
在每个列表项中显示图片的话 那么我们就可以在 Miwok 应用中执行类似的操作
Now let's get started by taking a look at the adapter class,
我们先来看看 Adapter 类
which is used to control how list items appear.
该类可以用来控制列表项是如何出现的
So to help us out, I'm going to type T on my keyboard, and
在键盘上按下 T
that triggers the file finder in GitHub.
在 GitHub 中调出文件查找器
I'm going to search up adapter, and it looks like here, there's a file called
搜索 adapter 看起来这里有个文件
Android flavor adapter, which sounds really similar to our word adapter.
叫做 AndroidFlavorAdapter 和我们的 WordAdapter 听起来很相似
Now, taking a look closer at this file, it looks like it does also extend from
再仔细观察下该文件 发现它也继承于
the ArrayAdapter class, but here, instead of holding word objects like our
ArrayAdapter 类 但是在此处发现 AndroidFlavorAdapter
word adapter does, the Android flavor adapter holds Android flavor objects.
并非像我们的 WordAdapter 那样 存储的是 Word 对象 它存储的是 AndroidFlavor 对象
So skimming down the code, we get to the getView method call, and
向下滚动代码 我们转到 getView 方法调用
all of this looks similar to our word adapter class.
所有这些都看起来和我们的 WordAdapter 类很相似
And down here, there's some code related to the ImageView.
在这里有一些和 ImageView 相关的代码
So here in this first line, we're searching through the listItemView
在第一行里 我们要在 listItemView 布局中进行搜索
layout to find the view with the ID list_item_icon.
查找 ID 为 list_item_icon 的视图
When we find that view, we cast it to an ImageView and
找到该视图后 我们将其传递给 ImageView
then store it in a variable called icon.
然后存储在叫做 Icon 的变量里
After that, we can call the setImageResource method on that
接着我们可以针对该 ImageView 调用 setImageResource 方法
ImageView, and into this method, we pass in an input of the image resource ID
并向此方法传入 AndroidFlavor 对象的
from the AndroidFlavor object.
图片资源 ID
So these two lines of code sets the right dessert image on the list item.
这两行代码将正确的甜点图片设置到了相应的列表项上
Let's take this information and do something similar in our Miwok app.
我们根据这一信息 对 Miwok 应用采取类似的操作
So here we are in the Miwok app.
转到 Miwok 应用
Now in the getView method of our WordAdapter,
在 WordAdapter 的 getView 方法中
let's find the imageView in the list item layout.
我们在列表项布局中找到该 imageView
Here in this line, I search for the listItemView layout for
在这行代码中 我在 listItemView 布局中
the view with the ID image.
搜索图片为该 ID 的视图
Once I find it, I store the view in a variable called ImageView.
找到后 我将该视图存储在 ImageView 变量中
Now do you remember where we assigned this view ID image?
还记得我在哪分配了这个视图 ID 图片吗？
Well, it was back here in the list item layout.
我是在 list_item 布局中分配的
So remember that we assigned the view IDImage to the ImageView here?
我们在这里将视图 ID 图片分配给了 ImageView
Now let's go back to the WordAdapter class.
现在回到 WordAdapter 类
Once we have the ImageView Java object, we can call a setImageResource method on
具有 ImageView Java 对象后 我们可以对其调用 setImageResource 方法
it, just like we saw in the Android flavor app.
就像在 Android Flavor 应用中看到的一样
Now in that method, we need to pass the ImageResourceId as its input.
在该方法中 我们需要传入 ImageResourceId 作为其输入值
And luckily, we can get that from the current word object by simply calling
幸运的是 我们可以直接通过调用 getImageResourceId 方法
the getImageResourceId method.
从 currentWord 对象中获得该 ImageResourceId
Great, so those were all the changes we needed.
太棒了 这些就是我们需要作出的所有更改
And let's run the app on our device now.
现在在设备上运行下该应用吧
So tapping through each activity,
点按每个 Activity
we can see the proper images loaded into our list view.
我们可以看到列表视图中加载了正确的图片
And it's looking really good.
看起来非常棒
And as we expected, the Phrases activity looks broken.
不出所料 PhrasesActivity 出现了问题
So we're going to fix that in the next exercise.
我们将在下个练习中解决该问题